epiphanysolutions.co.uk 2019-01-21

# Privacy Policy | Epiphany

## Jaywing plc Privacy Statement

Jaywing respects privacy and your rights to control your personal data. Our principle guidelines are simple; we will be clear about the data we collect and why. Your data is protected by us. We do not and will not sell or share your data to third parties.

This Privacy Statement (the 'Statement') explains the personal information we collect from you and how we will use it. The Statement also covers the choices you can make about the data we collect, and how you can control these decisions. It applies to all Jaywing plc companies, subsidiary brands and trading entities, their websites and their data collection and privacy practices.

Please read this Statement carefully to understand when you may provide personal information to us and how Jaywing uses and protects personal information provided. By using this website, you agree to the use of your personal information as described in this Statement. The terms 'we', 'us', or Jaywing’ are each intended as reference to Jaywing Plc and its subsidiaries.

### Company Structure

Jaywing plc is a UK AIM-listed Company that is comprised of a number of subsidiary brands and trading entities. Jaywing is a trading name for marketing services in the UK and Australia, comprising Scope Creative Marketing Ltd, Jaywing Central Ltd, Bloom Media (UK) Ltd, Massive Group Pty Ltd, Alphanumeric Ltd.

Jaywing Intelligence is a trading name for Jaywing plc’s marketing technology division Jaywing Innovations Ltd.

Jaywing PR is a trading name of Shackleton PR Ltd

Jaywing and Jaywing Risk are trading names for our specialist risk analytics consultancy Alphanumeric Ltd.

Jaywing and Jaywing Contact are trading names for our contact centre, HSM Ltd.

Epiphany is a trading name for marketing agency Epiphany Solutions Ltd.

Frank Digitial is a trading name for Frank Digital Pty Ltd.

Learning about Jaywing

As you gather more information about Jaywing, you may virtually or physically visit a site that we own. Examples include browsing our website, calling our offices, physically visiting a Company location or attending events. To learn more about our Company and our Services, you may voluntarily provide personal information, such as your name and email address during these interactions. You may also provide information online via cookies and other technology when you visit our websites.

## How we use Personal Information

### Communication, Marketing and Advertising

We use the data we collect to deliver and personalise our communications with you. For example, we may contact you by telephone, email, direct mail, via social channels or other means of electronic communication to inform you about Jaywing or our Services, new Products and Services, to update you on news or a topical issue, invite you to take part in a survey, or invite you to an event. We also use cookies and similar technologies to provide the most relevant information to you. For information about managing email subscriptions and promotional communications, please visit the How to Access and Control Your Personal Information section of this Statement.

For information on how we use the data we collect if you are applying for a job at Jaywing, please see our Recruitment section below.

### Sharing and Disclosure

Jaywing does not and will never sell or share personal information. We only use your data as authorised in this Statement.

### Your Communication, Marketing and Advertising Preferences

You can opt out of receiving certain direct communications from Jaywing. If you wish to stop receiving emails from us, you can do so by following the instructions included in every email sent to you via either the “Unsubscribe” tab for a system generated email or by replying with “UNSUBSCRIBE” in the subject line for a direct email. We respect your choice, and we will stop sending you promotional emails once you unsubscribe.

If you no longer wish to receive phone calls from Jaywing, tell us on the call or email mydata@jaywing.com.  If you no longer wish to receive direct mail from Jaywing, send an email to mydata@jaywing.com, call us on 0333 370 6500  or write to us at Marketing Opt Out, Jaywing, Albert Works, 71 Sidney Street, Sheffield S1 4RG.

It may take up to 4 week/s to process your request.

Please note, we will continue to communicate with you for issues relating directly to the Products/Services which you receive from us.

### How to Access and Control Your Personal Information

You can review, edit or delete your personal data by contacting us directly at mydata@jaywing.com.

You can always opt out of receiving promotional emails and other types of marketing communication from us.

### Cookies and Other Similar Technologies

We use various methods to help us personalise our website for you, remember your preferences, understand how users are using our websites, and help customise our marketing offerings including cookies, tracking pixels, referers’ IP addresses, how you interact with our website and environment variables. By visiting our website, you agree to the use of cookies and similar technologies for the purposes described in this Statement.

We collect: name, email address, IP address, your interactions with our website and information provided by third parties, cookies and similar technology.

Why: We use this information to share news and Products and Services offered by Jaywing. Additionally, the IP address helps us to understand geographic information about our website visitors better so that we can improve our website for everyone.

A cookie is an element of data that a website can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. It can then be used to provide you with tailored information. Cookies are used to better personalise the content that you and other users will see. We may use the information to research and understand how our users’ habits are similar or different so that we can enhance your experience on our site. We do not collect any personally identifiable data from cookie derived data without your permission.

You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it.

\-       A referrer is the information passed along by a web browser that references the web URL you linked from and it is automatically gathered by our web server. This information is used by Jaywing to identify broad demographic trends that may be used to provide information tailored to your interests.

\-       IP addresses are automatically gathered by our web server. Your IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer so that data (such as the web pages you request) can be sent to you. You will not be personally identified from this information.

\-       Environment variables we gather, usually through Google Analytics, include time, type of web browser being used, the operating system/platform, and CPU speed. This information is used for broad demographic information and personalising websites, such as serving small images to mobile devices.

\-       Third party cookies are those placed by websites and/or third parties. These cookies may be used on our website to improve our products or services or to help us provide more relevant advertising. These cookies are subject to the respective privacy policies for these external services, for example, [Google’s Data Use Policy](https://www.google.com/url?q=https://privacy.google.com/intl/en-GB/your-data.html&sa=D&ust=1527090525968000).

\-       Analytics cookies. We use analytics cookies like those offered by Google Analytics, to help us understand things about how our site is being used, like how long a visitor stays on our website, what pages they find most useful, and how they arrived at it.

How to control cookie settings

Most web browsers allow you to control cookies through their settings preferences, however if you limit the ability of websites to set cookies, you may impact your overall user experience. Below you can learn about how to control cookie settings on popular web browsers:

### Advertising and Modern Marketing Tools

We use several modern marketing tools in support of our advertising efforts.

Jaywing may work with third party advertisers that use cookies and similar technologies to provide more relevant advertising about our Products and Services on our website and across the internet. To provide this 'interest-based advertising', the parties combine non-personal data about your online activities acquired over time, which helps cater advertising that is delivered to you. Examples of this may include an advertisement on a Facebook page, or a Google owned page such as a search results page or YouTube, or on a site within Google’s advertising network. We do not share your personal information as part of this process. You can opt-out of these personalised ads from third party advertisers and ad networks who are members of the [Network Advertising Initiative (NAI)](https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp&sa=D&ust=1527090525971000) or who follow the [Digital Advertising Alliance's Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising](https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.aboutads.info/choices/&sa=D&ust=1527090525971000) by visiting the [opt-out pages on the NAI website](https://www.google.com/url?q=http://optout.networkadvertising.org/%23!/&sa=D&ust=1527090525971000) and [DAA website](https://www.google.com/url?q=http://optout.aboutads.info/%23!/&sa=D&ust=1527090525972000). Opting out may make the ads you see across the internet less relevant to you.

If you have opted out of receiving communications from us, we will not use your email for interest-based advertising, although you may still be subject to certain interest-based advertising depending upon your browser and device settings.

### Recruitment

You may wish to share personal information with Jaywing regarding employment opportunities. As part of the recruitment process, we may ask for your permission to hold your personal information. We will retain the information for two years, or for the duration of your application. If after this period, we have found no suitable vacancies, we will delete your information.

By submitting your details, you give permission for us to circulate your details for recruitment purposes across Jaywing plc as necessary.

We will not send marketing communications to you following a job application with Jaywing plc.

### Security

Jaywing is committed to protecting the security of your personal data. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal data from unauthorised access, use or disclosure. For example, we store the personal data you provide on computer systems that have limited access and are in controlled facilities. When we transmit data over the Internet, we protect it using encryption.

Jaywing takes suitable precautionary measures to help protect information about you from loss, theft, misuse and unauthorised access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. Your personal information is stored on servers that are kept in a controlled environment with suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure its access. While we take reasonable precautions to guard personal information we collect from you, no security system is impenetrable.

### Business Operations

We use data to develop business intelligence that enables us to operate, protect, make informed decisions, and report on the performance of our business.

## Other Important Privacy Information

### Where We Store and Process Personal Data

Personal data collected by us may be stored and processed in the UK or in any other country where Jaywing or its affiliates, subsidiaries or service providers maintain facilities.

### Our Retention of Personal Data

Jaywing retains personal data for as long as necessary to provide our Services, or for other essential purposes such as for recruitment, complying with our legal obligations, and resolving disputes and enforcing our agreements. Because these needs can vary for different data types in the context of different Products or Services, actual retention periods can vary.

### Links to Other Websites

Our websites may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave a Jaywing site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information that you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

### Changes to Our Privacy Statement

Jaywing may modify or update this Statement when necessary to reflect customer feedback and changes in our Products and Service; so, please review it regularly.

### How to Contact Us

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of or your dealings with this website, please contact us at mydata@jaywing.com.

If you have any questions about the use of your personal information, please send us an email to mydata@jaywing.com.

Unless otherwise stated, Jaywing is a data processor for personal data we collect through the Products and Services subject to this Statement.

Our registered address is Albert Works, 71 Sidney Street, Sheffield S1 4RG.

Jaywing is officially registered under the 1998 Data Protection Act with registration number 02715861.

Jaywing’s Data Protection Representative is Alan Paterson, IT Director. Epiphany’s Data Protection Representative is Ryan Scaife, Finance Director.

Epiphany Solutions Ltd is registered with the Information Commissioner’s Office under registration Z2137995

Your use of this website constitutes acceptance of our policy.
